Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center
1957-2022
1975-1997
New York University Archives
Grey Art Gallery & Study Center
New York University. Art Collection
RG.42.5
107 boxes
18.51 Gigabytes
The Grey Art Gallery and Study Center is New York University's fine arts museum and was established in 1975 due to a financial contribution by Abby Weed Grey. Its function is to collect, preserve, study, document, interpret, and exhibit the evidence of human culture. Building on the New York University's Art Collection, established in 1958, the gallery hosts exhibitions of local, national and international interest. The collection consists of correspondence, exhibit press releases, catalogs, catalog drafts, exhibit labels, exhibition checklists, floor plans, research materials, grant applications; shipping, transportation, and insurance information. The collection also includes a small amount of audio recordings, video recordings, and electronic records. The materials date from 1957 to 2019.
Conditions Governing Access
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was transferred to the University Archives from the Grey Art Gallery in November 2011, April 2012, and June 2012. Further accretions were transferred in October 2017, June 2018, January 2020, and July 2022. The accession numbers associated with these transfers are 12.016, 14.025, 15.041, 2017.050, 2018.019, 2019.089, 2020.017, and 2022.059.
Arrangement
The records are arranged into five series. Series II: Administrative Files has been further arranged into five subseries. The contents of each series are arranged chronologically in order of the exhibitions with the exception of Series III, which is arranged according to size. The series and subseries arrangement of the records is as follows:
Series I: Exhibition Files
Series II: Administrative Files Subseries A: Correspondence Subseries B: Grey Subseries C: WNYC Subseries D: Development Subseries E: Annual Reports
Series III: Oversize
Series IV: Publications
Series V: Photographs
Historical Note
The Grey Art Gallery is New York University's fine arts museum. Its function is to collect, preserve, study, document, interpret, and exhibit the evidence of human culture. Founded in 1974, by the philanthropist and art collector Abby Weed Grey, it is located in the Silver Center building at 100 Washington Square East and 33 Washington Place. The gallery distinguishes itself by emphasizing art's historical, cultural, and social contexts, with experimentation and interpretation as integral parts of programmatic planning. Thus, in addition to being a place to view the objects of material culture, the gallery serves as a museum-laboratory in which a broader view of an object's environment enriches our understanding of its contribution to civilization.
The Grey Art Gallery and Study Center was inaugurated on April 9, 1975. It is located on the site of the original New York University building (1835-1892). Here, in the early years of the university, the nation's first university art department, headed by Professor Samuel F. B. Morse, was established. In 1927 Albert E. Gallatin, son of an NYU chemistry professor, established what is considered to be the first museum of modern art in the United States on the same site. Originally called the Gallery of Living Art, it was later renamed the Museum of Living Art. The museum's collection consisted of contemporary paintings and drawings by creative and progressive artists. It was closed in 1943 for economic reasons.
In 1958, the New York University Art Collection was founded with the acquisition of Francis Picabia's "Resonateur" (ca.1922) and Fritz Glarner's "Relational Painting" (1949–50). Overseen by the NYU Art Committee and its head, curator Ruth Bowman, the collection continued to grow over the next decade and a half with the aid of alumni, artists and friends of the university. By the middle of the 1970s, the collection consisted of over 2000 paintings, sculptures, drawings, prints and photographs, with heavy concentration in modern art. It included works by such artists as Picasso, Leger and Hofmann. Many of the collection pieces were hung at separate locations throughout the university, with new acquisitions exhibited each year at the Contemporary Art Gallery in Loeb Student Center. However, due to the lack of available space, most of the artwork was kept in storage when not part of a special exhibition.
In 1974, Abby Weed Grey donated one million dollars for the establishment of The Grey Art Gallery and Study Center. Most of the donation funded construction of the gallery space. The remaining funds were set aside as a permanent endowment for the maintenance, display and exhibition expenses of the collection. New York University agreed to cover basic operating expenses in return. Mrs. Grey also donated a large collection of Middle Eastern and Asian art which she had assembled over the course of her life. This donation joined the New York University Art Collection, all of which was then housed in the newly established gallery. Mrs. Grey remained a frequent supporter of the gallery, giving another large donation in 1977 for the construction of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center Library of Fine Arts, with the stipulation that selections previously donated by the Ben and Abby Grey Foundation would be constantly exhibited in the library.
Upon its establishment, the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center was administered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, with Kenneth L. Mathis appointed its first director and Joy L. Gordon serving as its first curator. The Gallery showcased large exhibitions in the main hall of the building, with smaller exhibits staged in the small gallery and the gallery windows. Many of its programs and exhibitions have been made possible with the support of the National Endowment for the Arts, The National Endowment for the Humanities, and the New York State Council for the Arts. Among the more popular and unique exhibitions put on by the gallery are the Parviz Tanavoli exhibit of Persian art, sponsored by the Iranian government in honor of the American Bicentennial in 1976, and a series of exhibitions relating to AIDS in the late 1980s and early 1990s.
In the late 1970s, administration of the Grey Art Gallery shifted to the Office of External Affairs. When External Affairs was disbanded in the early 2000s, the gallery was administered by University Development and Alumni Relations (UDAR), until being transferred to its current home in the Office of the Provost in the late 2000s.
Sources: 1. Grey Art Gallery, "History and Mission," accessed July 20, 2015, available online at http://www.nyu.edu/greyart/info/info.html. 2. Grey Art Gallery, "About the Collection," accessed July 20, 2015, available online at http://www.nyu.edu/greyart/collection/collection.html.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials that have not been preserved may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact special.collections@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Access to audiovisual materials in this collection is available through digitized access copies. Researchers may view an item's original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Born-digital materials have not been transferred and may not be available to researchers. Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact special.collections@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Related Materials
Abby Weed Grey Papers (MC 151)
Scope and Contents
This collection documents the activities of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center and its predecessor, the New York University Art Collection. The records are largely concerned with the exhibitions created and hosted by the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center. Some records also relate to exhibitions of the New York University Art Collection at the Contemporary Art Gallery in New York University's Loeb Student Center. Collection materials date from 1957 to 2012.
Various formats of materials are included in the collection. Unpublished materials include the administrative records of the gallery; correspondence between the gallery and artists, lenders, funders, press and patrons; grant applications; exhibit planning materials, including exhibit labels, exhibition checklists, floor plans, research materials, and shipping, transportation, and insurance information; and photographs related to gallery exhibitions. Published materials include informational brochures about the New York University Art Collection and exhibition catalogs from the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center.
The collection also includes a small number of audio cassettes and VHS tapes of WNYU television and radio broadcasts related to the New York University Art Collection. Furthermore, there are electronic records on CD-R, Floppy Disk, and Zip Disk.
Art -- Study and teaching.; Artists.; Art museums -- New York (N.Y.); Art -- Exhibitions.; Lapel pins; Bowman, Ruth, 1923-; Mathis, Kenneth L.; Grey, Abby Weed, 1902-1983; Reynolds, Gary A.; Sokolowski, Thomas W.; Gordon, Joy L.; Littman, Robert; Gumpert, Lynn; Grey Art Gallery & Study Center
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-2004
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence between the gallery and artists, lenders, funders, press and patrons; grant applications; exhibit planning materials, including exhibit labels, exhibition checklists, floor plans; research materials from other institutions (including a small number of photographs and slides used for research but not for exhibition); and shipping, transportation, and insurance information; and photographs related to gallery exhibitions. The series also includes press releases, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, brochures, event invitations, exhibition catalogs, posters, postcards, memorandum, artist biographies, a small number of audio cassettes, and transparencies.
  - Exhibition History Files, undated; cuid2274 (Box I:1, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. Grey's Tour, undated; cuid2275 (Box I:1, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter Copies, 1958-1971; cuid2276 (Box I:1, Folder 3)
  - Publicity -- NYU Publications, 1961-1964; cuid2277 (Box I:1, Folder 4)
  - Publicity Magazines (1 of 2), 1961-1967; cuid2278 (Box I:1, Folder 5)
  - Publicity Magazines (2 of 2), 1961-1967; cuid2279 (Box I:1, Folder 6)
  - Publicity - NYU (1 of 2), 1961-1971; cuid2280 (Box I:1, Folder 7)
  - Publicity - NYU (2 of 2), 1961-1971; cuid2281 (Box I:1, Folder 8)
  - Harold Rosenberg Articles (1 of 2), 1961-1971; cuid2282 (Box I:1, Folder 9)
  - Harold Rosenberg Articles (2 of 2), 1961-1971; cuid2283 (Box I:1, Folder 10)
  - Symposia (The Unpopular Artist in Popular Culture), 1962 December; cuid2284 (Box I:1, Folder 11)
  - NYU Exhibition Catalogs (1 of 2), 1963-1968; cuid2285 (Box I:1, Folder 12)
  - NYU Exhibition Catalogs (2 of 2), 1963-1968; cuid2286 (Box I:1, Folder 13)
  - Exhibitions Sponsored By the NYU Art Collection, 1963-1973; cuid2287 (Box I:1, Folder 14)
  - Exhibition: Selections from the NYU Art Collection, 1963 March 6-20; cuid2288 (Box I:1, Folder 15)
  - Exhibition: Joseph Cornell, 1963 December 3-18; cuid2289 (Box I:1, Folder 16)
  - Exhibition: Bernard Childs, 1964 April 14-May 15; cuid2290 (Box I:1, Folder 17)
  - Exhibition of Paintings From the NYU Collection, 1964 September 14-October 9; cuid2291 (Box I:1, Folder 18)
  - Concrete Expressionism Exhibition, 1965; cuid2292 (Box I:1, Folder 19)
  - AFA Ancient Mexico Exhibit, 1965 January-March; cuid2293 (Box I:1, Folder 20)
  - AFA -- A University Collects, 1965 June-1968 February; cuid2294 (Box I:1, Folder 21)
  - Exhibition: Alumni Show, 1965 October 11-22; cuid2295 (Box I:1, Folder 22)
  - Exhibitions -- Recent Acquisitions, 1966; cuid2296 (Box I:1, Folder 23)
  - A Loan Exhibit from the NYU Collection (Gould Student Center), 1966; cuid2297 (Box I:1, Folder 24)
  - Sound Exhibition -- Loeb, 1966 March 4-18; cuid2298 (Box I:1, Folder 25)
  - Exhibition: Paul Brach, 1966 May 9-June 6; cuid2299 (Box I:1, Folder 26)
  - Form 99 Art Collection -- Picasso, 1966 August-November 1967; cuid2300 (Box I:1, Folder 27)
  - Exhibition: Contemporary Drawings, 1966 December 12-1967 January 6; cuid2301 (Box I:1, Folder 28)
  - Publicity -- A University Collects, 1966-1968; cuid2302 (Box I:1, Folder 29)
  - Aspects of American Realism, 1966-1976; cuid2303 (Box I:1, Folder 30)
  - Poem Paintings, 1967 January 9-February 5; cuid2304 (Box I:1, Folder 31)
  - Publicity, 1967 August-October; cuid2305 (Box I:1, Folder 32)
  - NYU Art Exhibition Benefit, 1967 September; cuid2306 (Box I:1, Folder 33)
  - Exhibition: Recent Acquisitions, 1967 September 15-October 9; cuid2307 (Box I:1, Folder 34)
  - The New York Painter (Marlborough-Gerson), 1967 September 27-October 14; cuid2308 (Box I:1, Folder 35)
  - Jean Tinguely -- "Man, Woman, Machine", 1967 December 11; cuid2309 (Box I:1, Folder 36)
  - Exhibition: Picasso Graphics, 1968 March 1-18; cuid2310 (Box I:1, Folder 37)
  - Selections from NYU Collection, 1968 April 27-May 4; cuid2311 (Box I:1, Folder 38)
  - 10th Anniversary of NYU Art Collection, 1968 September 9-October 2; cuid2312 (Box I:1, Folder 39)
  - Newsletters - Volume I-III, 1969-1972; cuid2313 (Box I:1, Folder 40)
  - Exhibition: Les Levine, 1969 January 20-February 20; cuid2314 (Box I:1, Folder 41)
  - Exhibition: Glassboro State College, 1969 October 1-31; cuid2315 (Box I:1, Folder 42)
  - Exhibition: Selections from NYU Art Collection, 1969 November 18-December 18; cuid2316 (Box I:1, Folder 43)
  - 100 Years of Impressionism (Wildenstein), 1970 April 2-May 9; cuid2317 (Box I:1, Folder 44)
  - Exhibition: Glassboro State College, 1971 April; cuid2318 (Box I:1, Folder 45)
  - Hudson River/NYU Publicity, 1971 September-October; cuid2319 (Box I:1, Folder 46)
  - 20th Century Painting and Sculpture from the NYU Art Collection, 1971 October 2-November 14; cuid2320 (Box I:1, Folder 47)
  - Exhibitions: University of Notre Dame, 1972-1973; cuid2321 (Box I:1, Folder 48)
  - Loeb Latin American Inst., 1972 September 14-October 5; cuid2322 (Box I:1, Folder 49)
  - Print Exhibition, 1973-1976; cuid2323 (Box I:1, Folder 50)
  - Exhibitions Print Show -- Hudson River Museum, 1973 January 13-March 4; cuid2324 (Box I:1, Folder 51)
  - Sandman Background Information, 1973 March-1977 July; cuid2325 (Box I:1, Folder 52)
  - Selections from the NYU Art Collection -- University of Connecticut, 1973 March 12-April 15; cuid2326 (Box I:1, Folder 53)
  - 15th Anniversary Exhibition -- Loeb, 1973 June 13-August 9; cuid2327 (Box I:1, Folder 54)
  - Exhibitions: University of Connecticut (1 of 2), 1973 March 12-April 15; cuid2328 (Box I:1, Folder 55)
  - Exhibitions: University of Connecticut (2 of 2), 1973 March 12-April 15; cuid2329 (Box I:1, Folder 56)
  - Press for Gallery Opening -- Clippings (1 of 2), 1974-1975; cuid2330 (Box I:1, Folder 57)
  - Press for Gallery Opening -- Clippings (2 of 2), 1974-1975; cuid2331 (Box I:1, Folder 58)
  - Irish Directors of the 70s -- Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1975; cuid2332 (Box I:2, Folder 1)
  - Irish Directors of the 70s -- Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1975; cuid2333 (Box I:2, Folder 2)
  - Recent American Etching -- Photographs, 1975-1976; cuid2334 (Box I:2, Folder 3)
  - American Abstract Artists, 1975-1975; cuid2335 (Box I:2, Folder 4)
  - Prints and Technique Exhibition, 1975 February 10-1976 May 3; cuid2336 (Box I:2, Folder 5)
  - Poster Show -- "Images of an Era: The American Poster", 1975-1976; cuid2337 (Box I:2, Folder 6)
  - Poster Show Clipping File, 1975 November-1977 June; cuid2338 (Box I:2, Folder 7)
  - Poster Exhibition -- PR, 1976; cuid2339 (Box I:2, Folder 8)
  - Poster Exhibition -- Invitations/Distribution, 1976; cuid2340 (Box I:2, Folder 9)
  - Poster Exhibition -- Shipping, 1976; cuid2341 (Box I:2, Folder 10)
  - Inaugural Exhibition -- Catalogue Copyright, 1975 April-1977 January; cuid2342 (Box I:2, Folder 11)
  - Aspects of American Realism -- Clippings, 1976 January-March; cuid2343 (Box I:2, Folder 12)
  - Prints and Techniques -- Press Releases, 1976 March 17; cuid2344 (Box I:2, Folder 13)
  - Prints and Techniques -- Clippings and Film File, 1976 March-April; cuid2345 (Box I:2, Folder 14)
  - Video Festival, 1976 April-May; cuid2346 (Box I:2, Folder 15)
  - Marjorie Strider BigBox PR, 1976 April 29-June 21; cuid2347 (Box I:2, Folder 16)
  - Parviz Tanavoli -- Locks from Iran Clipping File, 1976 February-December; cuid2348 (Box I:2, Folder 17)
  - Parviz Tanavoli -- Bob's File, 1976 March 18-May 12; cuid2349 (Box I:2, Folder 18)
  - Locks Show (1 of 3), 1976 May-1977 January 12; cuid2350 (Box I:2, Folder 19)
  - Locks Show (2 of 3), 1976 May-1977 January 12; cuid2351 (Box I:2, Folder 20)
  - Locks Show (3 of 3), 1976 May-1977 January 12; cuid2352 (Box I:2, Folder 21)
  - Tanavoli, 1976 June 23-1977 January 13; cuid2353 (Box I:2, Folder 22)
  - Parviz Tanavoli, 1976 August 5-November 9; cuid2354 (Box I:2, Folder 23)
  - Project Rebuild -- Udine Clippings, 1976 June 10-1977 September 2; cuid2355 (Box I:2, Folder 24)
  - Udine Exhibition Correspondence, 1976 June 25-September 7; cuid2356 (Box I:2, Folder 25)
  - Project Rebuild -- Udine Memos, 1976 July-August; cuid2357 (Box I:2, Folder 26)
  - Project Rebuild -- Udine Inviations, 1976 August 2; cuid2358 (Box I:2, Folder 27)
  - Project Rebuild -- Udine Checklists, 1976 August 11-27; cuid2359 (Box I:2, Folder 28)
  - Documentation -- Udine (1 of 2), 1976 August; cuid2360 (Box I:2, Folder 29)
  - Documentation -- Udine (2 of 2), 1976 August; cuid2361 (Box I:2, Folder 30)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy/Grosman -- Clips, 1976 August 22-1978 January 19; cuid2362 (Box I:2, Folder 31)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy/Grosman -- Checklist of Exhibition, 1977 February 1-March 4; cuid2363 (Box I:2, Folder 32)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy -- Essays by Christopher Scott, 1977; cuid2364 (Box I:2, Folder 33)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy -- Floor Plan, 1977 February-March; cuid2365 (Box I:2, Folder 34)
  - Avedisian/Hennessy/Grosman -- Invitations, 1977 February 1-March 4; cuid2366 (Box I:2, Folder 35)
  - Part II - Inaugural Exhibition -- Press Releases, 1976 September 2-14; cuid2367 (Box I:2, Folder 36)
  - Part II - Inaugural Exhibition -- Painting and Sculpture Clippings, 1976 September-October; cuid2368 (Box I:2, Folder 37)
  - Part II - Inaugural Exhibition -- Works in Show, 1976 September-October; cuid2369 (Box I:2, Folder 38)
  - Part II - Inaugural Exhibition -- Checklist, 1976 September-October; cuid2370 (Box I:2, Folder 39)
  - Inaugural Exhibition Part II - Letters to Donnors and Artists, 1976 September-October; cuid2371 (Box I:2, Folder 40)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Bob's File, 1941-1976; cuid2372 (Box I:2, Folder 41)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Clipping File, 1976 December-1977 May; cuid2373 (Box I:2, Folder 42)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Invitations, 1976-1977; cuid2374 (Box I:2, Folder 43)
  - England [Beatrix Potter], 1976-1977; cuid2375 (Box I:2, Folder 44)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Hunt Institute and Other Miscellaneous, 1903-1977; cuid2376 (Box I:2, Folder 45)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Souvenir Catalog, 1977; cuid2377 (Box I:2, Folder 46)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Checklist, 1977 January-May; cuid2378 (Box I:2, Folder 47)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Press Releases, 1977 March-May; cuid2379 (Box I:2, Folder 48)
  - Beatrix Potter -- Horn Magazine Articles, 1929-1977; cuid2380 (Box I:2, Folder 49)
  - Circa 1776 -- Salute to Cooper-Hewitt Invitations, 1965-1976; cuid2381 (Box I:2, Folder 50)
  - Circa 1776 -- Press Releases, 1976 October 25; cuid2382 (Box I:2, Folder 51)
  - Grossman -- Bob's Notes, 1977 February; cuid2383 (Box I:2, Folder 52)
  - Grosman -- Essay by Robert R. Littman, 1977 February; cuid2384 (Box I:2, Folder 53)
  - Gallatin -- To Do, 1977 February 2-May 15; cuid2385 (Box I:2, Folder 54)
  - Gallatin -- Photographs, 1977 March-April; cuid2386 (Box I:2, Folder 55)
  - Amnesty Poster Exhibition, 1977 March; cuid2387 (Box I:2, Folder 56)
  - Panoramic Photography -- Hand List of the Exhibit, 1977 May-September; cuid2388 (Box I:2, Folder 57)
  - Panoramic Photography -- Press Photos/Negatives, 1977 September; cuid2389 (Box I:2, Folder 58)
  - Gallery of Living Art, undated; cuid2390 (Box I:2, Folder 59)
  - Gallery of Living Art, undated; cuid2391 (Box I:2, Folder 60)
  - Gallery of Living Art Revisited - Gallatin Questionnaires, 1977 May-September; cuid2392 (Box I:2, Folder 61)
  - The Gallery of Living Art Revisited (1 of 2), 1978 November; cuid2393 (Box I:2, Folder 62)
  - The Gallery of Living Art Revisited (2 of 2), 1978 November; cuid2394 (Box I:2, Folder 63)
  - Exhibition: Sports Festival, circa 1970s; cuid2395 (Box I:3, Folder 1)
  - Sam Wagstaff Photography Checklists, 1978 February 3-March 26; cuid2396 (Box I:3, Folder 2)
  - Gallatin Photographs, 1978 September-October; cuid2397 (Box I:3, Folder 3)
  - New Deal for Art Newspaper Catalogue, 1977-1978; cuid2398 (Box I:3, Folder 4)
  - Changes in Perspective Essay, circa 1977-1978; cuid2399 (Box I:3, Folder 5)
  - Wilmarth/Sandman Essays, 1978 January 10-February 3; cuid2400 (Box I:3, Folder 6)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Henry J. Neils, 1957 May 28-1961 February 24; cuid2401 (Box I:3, Folder 7)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright, 1969-1976; cuid2402 (Box I:3, Folder 8)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Photographs, 1974-1978; cuid2403 (Box I:3, Folder 9)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Documents/Objects, 1976-1978; cuid2404 (Box I:3, Folder 10)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Checklist, 1978; cuid2405 (Box I:3, Folder 11)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Press Photos, 1978; cuid2406 (Box I:3, Folder 12)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Lecture (Donald Kalec), 1978 November 1; cuid2407 (Box I:3, Folder 13)
  - House of Iran Exhibition, 1978 April-December; cuid2408 (Box I:3, Folder 14)
  - House of Iran Exhibition, 1978 April-September; cuid2409 (Box I:3, Folder 15)
  - House of Iran Exhibition (1978 November 14-24), 1978 May-December; cuid2410 (Box I:3, Folder 16)
  - Turkish Show, 1978 December-1979 November; cuid2411 (Box I:3, Folder 17)
  - Balet/Palmer/Smyth Essays, 1978; cuid2412 (Box I:3, Folder 18)
  - Ann Lauterbach - Poems for Washington Place Windows, 1978 January 17; cuid2413 (Box I:3, Folder 19)
  - Tiffany - Burlingham Information, circa 1978-1979; cuid2414 (Box I:3, Folder 20)
  - Tiffany Bulletin, 1979; cuid2415 (Box I:3, Folder 21)
  - Tiffany - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979 March-1980 March; cuid2416 (Box I:3, Folder 22)
  - Life -- "Atlantic" Wainwright Article, 1972-1979; cuid2417 (Box I:17, Folder 29)